[{"answer": "Hey, the that place screwed me on that when they changed the law, and you know it!  Anyway, 'least I try shit, still got some dreams left... you're a goddamn waitress, what do you got", "docId": "nursebetty.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "... well, then you ain't got much", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Hmmmm.", "docId": "nursebetty.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "That's what I thought.  You better give me another example", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Stupid is trying to sell it to other people who are, by their very nature, untrustworthy", "docId": "nursebetty.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Stupid is calling people in that place who are affiliated with the rightful owners of the thing you stole, and trying to sell it to them. Right my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "nursebetty.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "It was my friend..", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "What 'look'", "docId": "nursebetty.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I wasn't done, I was just sick of hearing him whine. And you didn't take him out, you scalped him. Christ, I almost puked, did I tell you that", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Dr. my friend", "docId": "nursebetty.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No, I mean my friend. He's a surgeon", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I'm not. I just drove in from that place", "docId": "nursebetty.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I came for love. My fianc is here", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I can't find Loma Vista Hospital..", "docId": "nursebetty.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I don't believe this! You're the second person here who's told me that. That's like that place saying they never heard of that place", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " Either you're making a fool out of me because you get off on it, or you got serious problems. Which one is it?", "docId": "nursebetty.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I'M TALKING ABOUT DAVID my friend!", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Shhh! I heard you the first time", "docId": "nursebetty.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "If you didn't want to do it, you should have said so! Is this about gas money", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Huh", "docId": "nursebetty.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " Oh, umm, yes, this is my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "To a party in the that place", "docId": "nursebetty.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Yes. I'd never been in a place like that before", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "No, you believed her, we drove all the way to L.A. so that means you trusted her that much... so why's the rest of her story suddenly so kooky? Huh", "docId": "nursebetty.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I call it 'nutty' as my shit after I eat Almond Roca..", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "You know, I almost believe that... you're like a warm breeze that's suddenly blown into my life...  I said that to my friend, once, at her funeral, remember?..", "docId": "nursebetty.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Yes... maybe it was", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "...did I win some contest", "docId": "nursebetty.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Why are you screaming at me? I mean, what am I... why am I here? I don't..", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Thanks so much. You must get bothered by this kind of thing a lot", "docId": "nursebetty.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "No, that should be more tha", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " Do you know who I am", "docId": "nursebetty.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Do you know why I'm here", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I have... did it sound that bad", "docId": "nursebetty.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "my friend..", "qsentId": 36}]